{
    "subject": "resource/Chris_Carrabba",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Chris Carrabba is from United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9865458011627197,
            "question": "Is Chris Carrabba from the United States of America?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9392170906066895,
            "question": "Is Chris Carrabba American?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8141010403633118,
            "question": "Where is Chris Carrabba from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6992647051811218,
            "question": "Where was Chris Carrabba born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.653344988822937,
            "question": "To which nation does Chris Carrabba belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6333647966384888,
            "question": "What country is Chris Carrabba associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.631767988204956,
            "question": "In which country did Chris Carrabba grow up?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6193690299987793,
            "question": "What nationality is Chris Carrabba?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.604396402835846,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Chris Carrabba's origin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5054483413696289,
            "question": "What is Chris Carrabba's birthplace?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Chris Carrabba is from United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8772_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about Chris Carrabba's origin?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8772_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What nationality is Chris Carrabba?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8772_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which country did Chris Carrabba grow up?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8772_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8772_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8772_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8772_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8772_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8772_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8772_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8772_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8772_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8772_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8772_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The file_path and text sections all confirm that Chris Carrabba's birthplace is West Hartford, Connecticut, U.S., which implies that he is from the United States."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Chris Carrabba is from the United States.\" Specifically, it mentions his place of birth as West Hartford, Connecticut, U.S., and refers to him as an American singer and musician."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}